<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:shrinkMode="strict">
    <string name="app_name">Dissertation</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="channel_id">notif_channel_id</string>
    <string name="title">SIAS Quiz</string>
    <string name="not_at_all">not at all</string>
    <string name="slightly">slightly</string>
    <string name="moderately">moderately</string>
    <string name="very">very</string>
    <string name="extremely">extremely</string>
    <string name="main_act_string">Thank you for agreeing to participate in this study.
        Information about this study can be found in the settings.
        Please first allow permissions by toggling them in the settings, and then click the button below to start the SIAS evaluation.
        Once taken, the score will be displayed and then saved to your device.
        If you retake the test, the new score will not be saved.
        Please, do not clear any application space for the duration of the study.</string>
    <string name="yourid">Your personal unique ID is: </string>
    <string name="start_sias_test">Start SIAS Test</string>
    <string name="sias_url">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Social_Interaction_Anxiety_Scale</string>
    <string name="learn_more_url">https://gla-my.sharepoint.com/:w:/g/personal/2255541h_student_gla_ac_uk/EQNzGTwMrwRGhejo8hiLK74BQ5rXIRRy5n1eoZjvY0SohQ?e=Z8Pea3</string>
    <string name="shpref_prefix">level4dissertation2255541h</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">level4dissertationprefs</string>

    <!--    question strings-->
    <string name="q1">I get nervous if I have to speak with someone in authority (teacher, boss, etc.).</string>
    <string name="q2">I have difficulty making eye contact with others.</string>
    <string name="q3">I become tense if I have to talk about myself or my feelings.</string>
    <string name="q4">I find it difficult to mix comfortably with the people I work with.</string>
    <string name="q5">I find it easy to make friends my own age.</string>
    <string name="q6">I tense up if I meet an acquaintance in the street.</string>
    <string name="q7">When mixing socially, I am uncomfortable.</string>
    <string name="q8">I feel tense if I am alone with just one other person.</string>
    <string name="q9">I am at ease meeting people at parties, etc.</string>
    <string name="q10">I have difficulty talking with other people.</string>
    <string name="q11">I find it easy to think of things to talk about.</string>
    <string name="q12">I worry about expressing myself in case I appear awkward.</string>
    <string name="q13">I find it difficult to disagree with another’s point of view.</string>
    <string name="q14">I have difficulty talking to attractive persons of the opposite sex.</string>
    <string name="q15">I find myself worrying that I won’t know what to say in social situations.</string>
    <string name="q16">I am nervous mixing with people I don’t know well.</string>
    <string name="q17">I feel I’ll say something embarrassing when talking.</string>
    <string name="q18">When mixing in a group, I find myself worrying I will be ignored.</string>
    <string name="q19">I am tense mixing in a group.</string>
    <string name="q20">I am unsure whether to greet someone I know only slightly.</string>

    <!--    preference strings -->
    <string name="usage_stats_pref">usage_stats_pref</string>
    <string name="battery_opt_pref">battery_opt_pref</string>
    <string name="no_change">Setting not changed</string>
    <string name="manual_change">The option to disable this is turned on for the purpose of the study. Please do not manually go into the system settings and change it from there.</string>
    <string name="see_data_collection">See data collection</string>
    <string name="toggle_data_collection">Toggle data collection</string>
    <string name="data_collection_is_off">Data Collection is Off</string>
    <string name="data_collection_is_on">Data Collection is On</string>
    <string name="use_the_button_below_to_turn_on_and_off_the_data_collection">Use the button below to turn on and off the data collection.</string>
    <string name="keep_alive_service">keep_alive</string>
    <string name="alive_notif_text">Data is being collected in the background.</string>
    <string name="monitor_service">monitoring_service</string>
    <string name="boot_data_disabled">This is due to data collection being disabled in the app. Please click here to go to enable it.</string>
    <string name="boot_notif_title">Dissertation App Data Collection</string>
    <string name="see_personal_sias_pref">see_personal_sias_pref</string>

</resources>
